Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory10 Mss.B.B61.inventory10
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents P
  - Parsons, Irving R. (Box 69)
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 10; 1p.
  - Parsons, James W. (Box 69)
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 7; 1p.
  - Parsons, John E. (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 May 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 May 11; 1p.
  - Parsons, Mabel Holmes (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 21; 2p.
  - Parsons, MacIlvaine (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 17; 4p.
  - Parsons, N. M. (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1911 May 6; 2p.
  - Parsons, William Barclay (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 4
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 11
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 18
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 22
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 6
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 10
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 18
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 12
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 17
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 25
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 25
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 16
  - Partak, A.W. (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 4; 2p.
  - Paszkowski (Box 69)
    - To Boas, 1906 Sept.10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 June 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 July 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Nov. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 June 7
  - Patridge, Lelia E. (Box 69)
    - To Boas, 1894 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1894 Apr. 30; 1p.
  - Pattee, Richard (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1937 June 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 May 23; 1p.
  - Patterson, E.H. (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 8; 2p.
  - Patterson, Ernest Minor (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1940 Sept.26; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. to Dearborn, N.H., 1940 Dec. 17
    - From Boas, 1941 Aug. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 July 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Sept.23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Dec. 20; 1p.
    - Ernest Minor Patterson -- to Bertha C. Edel, 1940 Dec. 18; 1p.
  - Patterson, Henry C. (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 24; 2p.
  - Patterson, M.W. (Box 69)
    - To Boas, 1909 Sept.16
  - Patton, F.L. (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 6; 2p.
  - Pauer, Paul Siliceo (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 25
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan. 21; 1p.
  - Paul, Elliot H. (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1905 July 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 July 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - See Adams, J.T., April 30, 1940
  - Paul, Hans (Box 69)
    - Hans Paul -- to James Speyer, 1920 Aug. 16; 1p.
  - Paul, S. (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 12; 1p.
  - Paula (Box 69)
    See Paula Jacobs
  - Paulsen, Friedrich (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 13; 2p.
  - Pavolini, P.E. (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1931 June 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 May 24; 1p.
  - Pawley, James, A. (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 19; 1p.
  - Payne, George E. (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1937 Sept.16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept.20; 1p.
  - Paynter, Richard H. (Box 69)
    - To Boas, 1963 July 16; 1p.
  - Paytiamo, James (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept.29; 1p.
    - James Paytiamo -- to Bureau of American Indians, 1930 July 14; 2p.
    - (Enclosure in letter from Heye Foundation, Museum of American Indian-, July 29, 1930)
  - Peabody, Charles (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 11
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 17
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 28
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 5
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 21
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 19
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 26
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 4
    - From Boas, 1913 Aug. 4
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 24; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 28; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 22; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Sept.29
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 5; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 11; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 18; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 6
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 23
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 7
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Nov. 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 19
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 21
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 23
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 6
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 19
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 14
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 1
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 27
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 2
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 18
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 25
    - To Boas, 1916 Sept.16
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 1
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 24
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 8
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 June 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Oct.; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 June 29; 2p.
    - Charles Peabody -- from New Era Printing Co., 1914 Dec. 29
  - Peabody, George Foster (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 18
    - From Boas, 1918 June 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Feb. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 May 5; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 May 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept.13; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 11; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 May 19; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 June 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Sept.24; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 May 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 15
    - To Boas, 1909 Nov. 19
    - To Boas, 1915 Sept.18
    - To Boas, 1918 June 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 May 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 May 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 June 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1924 May 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 May 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 5; 1p.
    - (Enc: Ballanta, N.G.J. General Statement of tour in West.Africa and reasons for a year's stay in Europe), 1926 Sept.29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 May 25; 1p.
    - George F. Peabody -- to O.G.Villard, 1912 May 13
    - George F. Peabody -- from R.S.Woodward, 1907 May 9
  - Peabody, John Foster (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1920 Feb. 17; 1p.
  - Peake, Cyrus H. (Box 69)
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 5; 1p.
  - Pearce, J. E. (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1919 July 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 5; 2p.
  - Pearl, Raymond (Box 69-70)
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 May 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1928 May 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Aug. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 6; 2p.
    - (Enc: Financial statements of the American Ethnological Society), 1931 Oct. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Mar. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Mar. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Sept.25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 July 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Aug. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 30
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 May 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Feb. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 May 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 June 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 June 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Sept.26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 May 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 3; 2p.
    - Raymond Pearl -- from A. Hrdlicka?, 1931 Oct. 13
  - Pearse, Edward M. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1927 June 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 June 14; 1p.
  - Pearson, Karl (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1905 Aug. 23
    - To Boas, 1893 July 22; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1897 May 20; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1897 Nov. 22; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Sept.7
  - Pearson, Paul M. (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 6; 1p.
  - Pearson, Walter J. (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 30; 2p.
  - Pearson Publishing CO. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 1; 1p.
  - Peary, R.E. (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1893 July 3
  - Peaslee, Rachel (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 5; 1p.
  - Pechmann, Wilhelm Frhr. v. (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 3; 2p.
  - Peck, C. D. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1906 Aug. 15
    - From Boas, 1906 Aug. 21
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 4
  - Peck, E. J. (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1897 Apr. 1; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1923 July 26; 1p.
  - Peck, F. E. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 14; 1p.
  - Peck, H. T. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1910 July 2
    - From Boas, 1910 July; 3p.
  - Peck, Walter (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1933 June 22; 1p.
  - Peckham, W.C. (Box 70)
    - W. G. Peckham -- to H. C. Kudlich, 1904 Nov. 23; 1p.
  - Pederson, Victor C. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1923 May 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 7; 1p.
  - Peebles, Rose Jeffries (Box 70)
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain, Replies., Jan. 1938
  - Peel, Roy V. (Box 70)
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies., Jan. 1938
  - Peery, W.K. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 9; 1p.
  - Peet, Stephen D. (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1888 Sept.13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1907 June 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 2; 2p.
  - Pegram, George B. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 June 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 June 11; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Sept.28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 28; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Feb. 17; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 June 8; 1p.
    - George B. Pegram -- to Cabanellas, 1937 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - George B. Pegram -- to Columbia Univ. Executive Officers, Anthrop. Dept., 1936 June 15; 1p.
    - George B. Pegram -- to Cabanellas, Feb. 11, 1937
      - NYC TLS, 1p.
      - co-signers:
        - Boas, F.
        - Carman, H.L.
        - Chamberlain, J.P.
        - Clarke, H.T.
        - Cuyler, H.F.
        - Dewey, John
        - Dunn, L.C.
        - Fries, H.L.
        - Gifford, J.P.
        - Hale, R.T.
        - Handler, Milton
        - Lynd, R.S.
        - Llewellyn, Karl
        - Michael, Jerome
        - Mitchell, W.C.
        - Randall, J.H., Jr.
        - Routestrauch, W.
        - Schelting, A. von
        - Siceloff, L.P.
        - Tamentmun, Frank
        - Walker, S.C.
        - Wallace, S.C.
        - Wolman, Leo
  - Peiser, Dr. J. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Oct. 7; 1p.
  - Peixotto, Ernest (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1923 May 7; 1p.
  - Pekarsky, Herman M. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 27; 1p.
  - Pellicer, Cesars (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 24; 1p.
  - Peltenberg, C. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1906 Aug. 15
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 21
    - To Boas, 1912 June 8
    - To Boas, 1912 June 21
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 6
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 19
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 26
    - C. Peltenberg -- to B. Laufer, 1906 July 31
  - Penafiel, Antonio (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 3
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 10
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 6
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1916 Mar. 15
  - Penard, T.E. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1916 Mar. 15
    - To Boas, 1917 June 23
    - T.E. Penard -- to H.A. Andrews, 1917 June 20
  - Penck, Albrecht (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1906 May 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 24; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 June 24; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 18
    - From Boas, 1920 Feb. 4; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Feb. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Feb. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 24; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 May 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Sept.20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 18; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 June 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 27
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 13
    - To Boas, 1912 June 14
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 4
    - To Boas, 1920 Jan. 6; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 21; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 27; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 July 26; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 5; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 May 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 June 28; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Sept.11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 26; 3p.
    - See Defaut, A., ? Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Nov. 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Sept.29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 23; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 19; 6p.
  - Pendray, Edward G. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1937 May 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 May 22; 1p.
  - Pendreigh, F.M. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 19; 1p.
    - See Speyer, James -, 8-24-20
    - F.M. Pendreigh -- from F.W.J. Heuser, 1920 Dec. 9
  - Penhallow, D.P. (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1898 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 9; 1p.
  - Penniman, T. K. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 20; 1p.
  - Penningroth, P.W. (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 June 1; 80p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec.end; 5p.
    - P.W. Penningroth -- to American Community Committee, 1930 Dec. end; 1p.
  - Pennock, Edward (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 26
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 25
  - People's Publishing Co. (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. end; 1p.
  - Pepper, George (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1893 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 May 17
    - To Boas, 1905 Sept.7
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 21
  - Perea, J. A. (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 23; 1p.
  - Perea, S. (Box 70)
    - See Perea, J.A., Jan. 23, 1934
  - Perkins, A.E. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1920 May 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 19; 1p.
  - Perkins, Frances (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1937 July 12; 1p.
  - Pernot, H. (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1929 June 19; 3p.
  - Perry, Bliss (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1941 July 31
      (see Boas, F. to Carlson, A.J.)
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 1; 1p.
  - Perry, Edward DeLavan (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 May 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Feb. 27
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1903 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 31
    - To Boas, 1904 May 7
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 9
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 15
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 2
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 25
    - To Boas, 1906 May 2
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 31
  - Perry, Katherine (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1934 May 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 23; 1p.
  - Perry, M. B. (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 13; 1p.
  - Perry, Ralph Barton (Box 70)
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies., Jan. 1938
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 4; 1p.
  - Perry, W. H. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 29; 1p.
  - Persons, W. Frank (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 9
    - To Boas, 1907 July 22
  - Perthes, Justus (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1888 Feb. 16; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1885 Feb.?
    - To Boas, 1888 Mar. 6; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1892 Aug. 3
  - Pescheck (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 19; 1p.
  - Pessar, Harry T. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 June 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 May 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Sept.23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 July 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 June 29; 1p.
  - Petain, Philippe (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1941 Nov. 27; 1p.
      (Enc: Boas, F. and others Petition)
  - Pete, Blanche (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Aug. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Sept.27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 14; 1p.
  - Peters, Harold N. (Box 70)
    NM
    - From Boas, 1933 June 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 May 26; 1p.
  - Peters, John P. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1941 July 31
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. end; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 July 31; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Sept. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Sept.16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 7; 1p.
  - Petersen-Borstel (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - (Enc: with Kallman, Franz -, Oct. 26, 1936)
  - Peterson, Joseph (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 7; 1p.
  - Peterson, Otto (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 19; 1p.
  - Peterson, Sadie M. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1923 May 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 May 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Jan. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May?; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Dec. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923???; 2p.
  - Petit, L.D. Jr. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 11; 1p.
  - Petrius, Custav (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1910 June 5
  - Petroff, Gregory (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1929 May 15; 1p.
  - Petrullo, Vincenzo (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1935 May 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 24; 1p.
  - Petter, Rudolphe (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Sept.19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 June 26
    - To Boas, 1927 Aug. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - Rudolphe Petter -- from I.W. Dunsey, 1940 Mar. 20
  - Petter, Mrs. Rudolphe (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1927 May 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 May 14; 2p.
  - Pettit, Katherine R. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 9
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 2
    - To Boas, 1907 Sept.2
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 28
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan.?; 9p.
  - Peza, Adriana de la (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 25
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 30
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 8
  - Pezet, A. Washington (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1925 May 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 May 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 May 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 May 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 May 20; 1p.
  - Pfeifer, George A. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 8; 1p.
  - Pfizenmayer, Charles F. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 28; 1p.
  - Pflüger, W. Alexander -- see also Zinger A (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 July 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 July 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 July 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Sept. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 July 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Sept. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 17
      - (see Enc. with Silliman, R.D., Apr. 17, 1933)
    - To Boas, 1933 June 7; 1p.
      - (Enc: with Schneider, K. to Jarres, June 7, 1933)
  - Phelps, Eleanor M. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1928 June 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 June 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 May 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 May 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 June 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 June 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 June 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 12; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. May 14, 1929, 1936 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 May 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 8; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 1; 4p.
    - See Boas, F. Open letter, 1939 Feb. 27
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 23; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1939 May 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 May 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 June 16; 3p.
    - Eleanor M. Phelps -- to R.W. Bryan, 1935 June 21; 1p.
  - Philippi, Alfred (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 16; 1p.
  - Philippi, R. A. (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1888 Mar. 7; 1p.
  - Philippine Islands-Bureau of Educ. (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Sept.6; 1p.
  - Phillips, Andrew W. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 6
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 24
    - From Boas, 1906 May 1
    - From Boas, 1906 May 19
    - From Boas, 1906 May 23
    - From Boas, 1906 June 7
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 5
    - From Boas, 1908 May 20
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 23
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 25
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 30
    - To Boas, 1906 May 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 May 8
    - To Boas, 1906 May 17
    - To Boas, 1906 May 24
    - Andrew W. Phillips -- from N. D. Harris, 1907 Feb. 1
    - Andrew W. Phillips -- to N.D. Harris, 1907 Feb. 5
    - Andrew W. Phillips -- to N.D. Harris, 1909 May 24
  - Phillips, E.F. (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 17
  - Phillips, G. B. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 28; 2p.
  - Phillips, Harold C. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 7; 1p.